(Supported by NRTA's Online Audiovisual
Quality Creation & Distribution Project)
(In the 21st year of King Xiang,)
(Jinan City fell.)
(Three hundred thousand civilians
were slaughtered.)
(Father!)
(Mother!)
(The Shaman Clan of Chu State
fell with the army.)
(I alone remain.)
(Burning bones as candles)
(to see the way home.)
(Flesh and blood as guide)
(to call my soul to its end.)
(The Phoenix descends
upon the mortal world.)
(Defying fate for rebirth!)
(I, the shamaness Chu Li,)
(offer my flesh and blood as sacrifice,)
(all to reverse time!)
Li.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
=Reunion Across Time=
=Episode 1=
(49 Days Before the City Falls)
(Wasn't I already dead?)
(Chu Li, Shamaness)
(This place...)
(It's so familiar.)
Have I been reborn?
Shamaness Chu Li,
(Yun Hua)
you abused shamanic arts
(Shamaness)
and murdered the innocent.
Such evil must be slain.
(This is)
(49 days ago)
(when I was falsely accused
of being a Flower Demon.)
(I made it.)
(Time has reversed,)
(and I have a chance
to save everything.)
Instead of repenting, you dare laugh?
Today,
I'll purge the Shaman Clan of a traitor.
(Kill her! Kill her!)
We're both of the Shaman Clan.
What right do you have to punish me?
Now, the Grand Shaman is in seclusion.
I'd like to see
who can save you now.
(Kill her!)
(Kill her! Kill her!)
(If I let Yun Hua have her way)
(like I did in my previous life,)
(I'll be driven out of Jinan City.)
(This time around,
I'll become Grand Shaman.)
(Only then can I persuade the King
to move the capital)
(and save everyone.)
The one in the cage
was harmed by your shamanic arts.
Yet you still show no remorse.
I'll have to show no mercy then.
Fire can't harm her.
You evil creature!
You're selfish and treacherous,
framing others for crimes.
Which of us is truly the evil one?
Stop!
(Song Ziyuan, Diviner of Chu State)
It's him?
(I'm sorry.)
Who are you?
Diviner Song,
what's the meaning of this?
(So he's Song Ziyuan,)
(a favorite of the King.)
(I didn't know him in my previous life.)
(At this point in my previous life,)
(he hadn't shown up either.)
(So why did he appear this time?)
Why such a commotion?
Recently in the city,
many young men and women
have been possessed
by plants and mutated.
In the end, they either
suddenly attack people
or die from the mutation.
And since childhood,
Chu Li has excelled at
controlling flowers, birds, insects,
and beasts.
She's the prime suspect.
As you said, I'm a mere suspect.
What right have you to convict me?
Punishing a member of the Shaman Clan
is the Grand Shaman's affair.
When did you gain such authority?
I...
I oversee all affairs
of the Shaman Clan.
Now,
take her into custody.
After the Grand Shaman leaves seclusion,
we will deal with her.
Wait.
(He actually means to lock me up?)
(Then I won't be able to do anything.)
Chu Li,
you dared to control a demon
to attack Diviner Song?
Did you see me do it?
I just saved him.
Who knows?
Maybe you staged the whole thing.
Guards.
My lord.
Take this demon
and Shamaness Chu Li
into custody.
Yes.
(Is he good or evil?)
(Why did he kill me
in my previous life?)
Even if you escape this time,
you won't escape death in the end.
(Flower Demon)
Don't move.
If it bites you,
you're dead.
You actually escaped.
Miss Chu Li, what's the meaning of this?
Can't you tell?
I'm here to kill you.
If you kill me,
then you'd best leave Jinan City soon.
Who said I'm leaving Jinan City?
You've been expelled
from the Shaman Clan
and accused of murder.
If you don't leave Jinan City,
do you mean to stay and await your doom?
Or is it that
you can't bear to leave your mother?
Xiuxiu.
My mother?
How do you know my mother?
The Shaman Clan
is under my jurisdiction.
Your relationship
with Grand Shaman Yaohua
may fool others,
but not me.
(Since he has such power,)
(perhaps I should let him)
(help me become Grand Shaman.)
If you spare me today,
I will clear your name
and help you leave Jinan City.
I told you,
I don't want to leave Jinan City.
Not only that,
I will become the Grand Shaman.
Why do you want to become Grand Shaman?
Diviner Song,
is it so hard to understand?
Among the Shaman Clan's shamanesses,
who wouldn't want
to become Grand Shaman?
Rest assured,
once I become Grand Shaman,
I'll be your most obedient dog,
Diviner Song.
You want to be my dog?
Your lapdog.
(I'm your most obedient dog.)
You still say such outrageous things.
Seal it with a handclasp.
Miss Chu Li,
you've been expelled
from the Shaman Clan
and have no merit.
I advise you to leave Jinan City soon.
(Love's)
(debt)
(is hard)
(to repay.)
My merit?
Here it comes.
♪Night rain falls in the courtyard,
shining on mortal partings♪
♪Strangers meet again,
past lives gleam in endless hues♪
♪A sharp arrow pierces memory♪
♪Longing spreads like dye♪
♪Beaded curtains
keep love and hate apart♪
♪Through boundless grief,
love remains hard to sever♪
♪A past bond, a parting dream;
when cold ends, purest joy remains♪
♪That year,
pear blossoms, verse, and laughter♪
♪One night, snow fell in wild flurries♪
♪All perfection in this world
hides regret♪
♪A drop of heart's blood seals love♪
♪No more longing enters dreams♪
♪When all turns to mist,
may you and I be safe forever♪
♪Through boundless grief,
love remains hard to sever♪
♪A past bond, a parting dream;
when cold ends, purest joy remains♪